Preliminary Guide to the North American Conference on British Studies records, 1949-2015 MS2187
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Executive Secretary records, 2001-2004; Series 2; 64 digital object(s)
  - nacbs annual reports, 2002-2003; Series 2 Subseries 1; 44 digital object(s)
    - 2003 reports, Series 2 Subseries 1; 10 digital object(s)
      - Ex Sec Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - IHR Mellon Fellowships Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - JBS Editors Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Program Chair Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Treasurer's Statement 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Webmaster Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - 2004 reports, 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 1; 24 digital object(s)
      - UCP Marketing Report, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 1; 6 item(s) digital objects
        - Appendix III_JSTOR_JBS.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
        - Appendix_II_UCP_Web_Stats_JBS.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
        - Sectn2, AppI, JBS04.doc [Section Two: Marketing Plan], 2004; Series 2 Subseries 1
        - Appendix IV_Comp JBS 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
        - Appendix V_MergeAnncmnt JBS 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
        - JBS2004_SectionOne.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Albion Report 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Albion Report, 2004.rtf, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Canadian Undergrad Essay Contest Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Canadian Undergrad Essay Contest Report, 2004.rtf, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Councilminutes'03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Exec Comm Minutes, Portland 2003.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Exec Comm Minutes, Portland 2003.rtf.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Exec Secy Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Exec Secy Report, 2004.rtf.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - JBS Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - JBS Report, 2004.rtf.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - NACBS Budget Info, 2004.xls, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - NACBS Budget, Prize Recipients, 2004.xls, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Program Committee Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Treasurer's Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Treasurer's Report, 2004.rtf.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Webmaster's Report, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Webmaster's Report, 2004.rtf.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Future of Albion Report.doc, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1
  - nacbs elections, Series 2 Subseries 2; 7 digital object(s)
    This subseries contains ballots and biographies for candidates in NACBS elections in 2002-2004.
    - Election Bios.doc, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - NACBS 02 Ballot.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - NACBS 2003 Ballot.doc, Series 2 Subseries 2
    - NACBS Ballot, 2004.doc, Series 2 Subseries 2
    - NACBS Election Bios, 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - NACBS Nominee Biographies, 04.doc, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Proposed Procedures for Elections.doc, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2
  - nacbs minutes and agendas, 2001-2003; Series 2 Subseries 3; 13 digital object(s)
    The digital objects in this subseries are stored off-line. Please see staff for assistance.
    This subseries contains meeting agendas and minutes for the NACBS Council and Executive Committee. These records date from 2001-2003.
    - minutes and agendas 2001, Series 2 Subseries 3; 2 digital object(s)
      - Council Minutes, Toronto.doc, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - Exec Minutes, Toronto.doc, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - minutes and agendas 2002, Series 2 Subseries 3; 5 digital object(s)
      - Council Minutes, Baltimore 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - Ex Comm Minutes, Balto 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - Exec Minutes, SF 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - NACBS Council Agenda 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - NACBS Exec Comm Agenda 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - minutes and agendas 2003, Series 2 Subseries 3; 3 digital object(s)
      - NACBS Council Agenda 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - NACBS Ex Com Agenda 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - Ex Com Agenda, Portland, 8-03.doc, 08/2003; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - minutes and agendas 2004, Series 2 Subseries 3; 2 digital object(s)
      - Ex Com Agenda, Philly, 10-27-04.doc, 10/27/2004; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - NACBS Council Agenda, Philly, 10-28-04.doc, 10/28/2004; Series 2 Subseries 3
      - NACBS Exec Comm Minutes, 10-04.doc, 10/2004; Series 2 Subseries 3
- President's records, 1971-2009; Series 3; 3.75 Linear Feet
  Organized into five subseries by past president: Barbara Shapiro, Reba Soffer, Walter Arnstein, Martin Wiener, and Barbara Harris.
  This series containes correspondence, reports, by-laws, surveys, elections, meeting minutes and other materials amassed by the acting president.
  - Barbara Shapiro records, 1983-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21)
    - Publications, 1983-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Committee and council lists, 1984-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Albion, 1986-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Journal of British Studies, 1987-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Treasure reports, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Nomination Committee and elections, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Reba Soffer records, 1984-1997; Series 3 Subseries 2
    Gift of Reba Soffer and Walter Arnstein, February 24, 2010 (2010.007)
    - Articles of incorporation, 1964-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Love Prize, journal lists, 1984-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Archives of NACBS, 1989-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation year fellowship, 1988-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Membership list, 1988-1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Endowment and fund raising, 1989-1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Nomination committee, 1989-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - British Council, 1990-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - British Council prize, 1990-1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Committee of NACBS, 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence miscellaneous, 1990-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Council, 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Executive committee, 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Regional meetings, 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Job descripton, 1990-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Memo on cooperation, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Planning report, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Prizes, 1990-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Regional meetings, 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Snow Prize, 1990-1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Albion, 1991-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - ACLS, 1991-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - AHA meeting, 1991-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Biography series, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Brundage's discs, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - By-laws, 1991-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Current research in British studies, Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Intelligencer, 1991-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Organizational structure NACBS, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Programs, 1991-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - San Jose, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Anglo-American conference, 1992-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Boulder, 1992-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Memberships and reports, 1992-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Publications (journals), 1992-1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Regional officers, 1992-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's reports, finances, 1992-1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Journal of British studies, 1993-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Montreal, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Life time awards, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - National portrait gallery, 1994-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Vancouver, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Insurance, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Royal historical society, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Royal Society for Arts, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Washington, 1995-1997; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - History of NACBS, undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Walter Arnstein records, 1994-1999; Series 3 Subseries 3
    - British Council, 1994-1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Carolina's symposium, 1994-1996; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Journal of British Studies, 1994-1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Prize committees, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Albion, 1995-1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Meetings, 1996-1998; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, 1996-1999; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Biography, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Meetings, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Martin Wiener records, 1971-2004; Series 3 Subseries 4
    Gift of Martin Wiener, May 7, 2010 (2010.027) and July 29, 2019 (2019.064)
    Arranged loosely chronological.
    - Conference on British Studies, 1971-1981; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Conference on British Studies [1/2], 1982-1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Conference on British Studies [2/2], 1982-1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - NACBS Basic Documents, 1984-2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - NACBS endowment comm., 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - NACBS Council, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - NACBS Council, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - NACBS, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Appointments to committees, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Annual conference, financial statements, 1999-2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - IHR, 1999-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Ad hoc committee report, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Executive council meeting, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Regional memos, 1999-2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - NACBS survey replies, 1999-2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - NACBS, 11/1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Associate executive secretary responses, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - British council, 2000-2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hotel contracts, 2000-2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - NACBS British council, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Executive meeting, 1/2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Executive committee, 10/2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Fundraising, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Meeting arranger, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Annual meeting schedule, 2000-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Pasadena, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Prizes, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Conference RHS, 2000-2004; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - British council, 2001-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Conference planning materials, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Executive meeting, 2001-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - NACBS British council Canada, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Executive secretary, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - NACBS council, 2001-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - NACBS elections, 2001-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - NACBS executive meeting, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - NACBS executive meeting, 10/2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - NACBS Program committee, 2001-; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - NACBS Toronto, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - NACBS Toronto, 11/2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Paid executive secretary, 2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - NACBS Baltimore meeting [Southern], 2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Journals, 2001-2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Re: publishing journals, 2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Participants lists, miscellaneous materials, undated; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - NACBS, Baltimore, 2002 November 6-10; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - NACBS report summary, 2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - NACBS brochure, 2002; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Council, 2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - NACBS Portland meeting, 2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - NACBS Exec. Comm. (Chicago), 2003 January; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Philly, 2004; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - NACBS Denver, 2005 October 5-9; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - NACBS, 2004; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Harris records, 1993-2012; 2005-2009; Series 3 Subseries 5; 1 Linear Feet
    Biographical / Historical
    Barbara Harris was president of the NACBS from fall 2007 to fall 2009. Trained in Tudor-Stuart English history, Harris's research and writing in the last two decades has focused on English aristocratic women in the period 14501550. She was awarded a Mellon Emeritus Fellowship in 2008.
    This subseries contains the correspondence, financial records, and conference records. These materials date from 1993-2012. The bulk dates are 2005-2009. These fiiles were maintained by Barbara Harris during her time as president.
    Gift of Dane Kennedy, February 17, 2012 (2012.019)
    Arranged chronologically.
    - NACBS basic information, 1993-2007; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Council meeting, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Council meeting, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Exec. committee, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Local arrangements guide, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Smith Barney, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Council meeting, 2006; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Council, 2006; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - NACBS Exec. Committee, 2006; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - JBS Univ. of Chicago, 2006-2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Council meeting, 2007; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Exec. Committee, 2007; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Council meeting, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Council, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Exec. Committee, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - NACBS meeting, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - ACLS and NUA, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - AHA meeting relations with AHA, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Brochure for local arrangements, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Canadien UG Prize, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Financial records, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - IHR Miles Taylor, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - [Meeting data], 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      General
      Note that the original folder title, the one written currently on the folder, does not match nor is reflective of items in folder. The folder title in this finding aid was created by staff and is reflective of the material within the folder.
    - Nonprofit coordinating committee of NY, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Program Committee meetings, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Webmaster and webpage, 2008; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Business meeting, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Exec. Committee, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Council, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - [Conference], 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - JBS editor, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Long-term planning, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Program, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's report, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - [Prof. Auchness??] Conference, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Philippa Levine, 2009; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - NACBS, 2012; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Records of Susan Groag Bell, 1999-2001; Series 4; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Susan Groag Bell is a historian connected to the Institute for Research on Women and Gender at Stanford. She edited an important anthology on European Women's History and wrote an important article on Medieval Women Book Owners that appeared in the publication Signs.
  Material in this series relates to the Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies and covers the years 1999-2001.
  Gift of Susan Groag Bell, February 25, 2011 (2011.017)
  - Reports and participants lists, 1999-2000; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies- Topics, 2001; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies- Catering materials, 2001; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British studies - attendance, invoices [1 of 2], 2001; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British studies - attendance, invoices [2 of 2], 2001; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2001; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Records of Linda Levy Peck, 1990-2000; Series 5; 1.5 Linear Feet 1 box
  This series contains correspondence, meetings minutes, reports and memoranda pertaining to the North American Conference on British Studies.
  - Linda Levy Peck, 1990-2000 (Box 32)
  - NACBS: Nominating Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Search for new editor of JBS, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - NACBS, 1982-1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - AHA/Chicago/2000, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - AHA/Boston/2001, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - AHA San Francisco 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - NACBS - AHA - 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - NACBS Council Mtg Min 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Executive Comm Mtg Min @ NACBS annual mtg 1999-2000, 1999-2001 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Executive Comm Mtg Min @ AHA 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - NACBS - General Correspondence and Charge of the Office, 1982-1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - NACBS- Membership, including correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - NACBS - Council and Annual Business Meeting Minutes, 1989-1995 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - AHA Annual Meeting, 1995 - Chicago, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - NACBS - Endowment Fund, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Email File, 1995-1998 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Albion, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - JBS/NACBS, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Intelligencer, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Restructuring NACBS, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Vancouver 1994 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Washington, D.C. 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - NACBS: Publication Comm., 1984-1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Chicago/1996, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Asilomar 1997 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Colorado Springs 1998, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - AHA/NYC/1997, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - AHA/Seattle/1998, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - AHA/Wash., D.C./1999, 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - NACBS/Boston/1999, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - NACBS - Pasadena 2000 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - NACBS - Toronto - 2001, 1999-2001 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - NACBS - Baltimore 2002 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Banner, "North American Conference on British Studies" (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Record donated by Dane Kennedy, 1999-2015; MS2187 Series 6; Kennedy, Dane Keith; 1 Linear Feet 2 document boxes
  This series contains records collected by Dane Kennedy of aspects of the governance and annual meetings of the NACBS covering the years 1999-2015.
  Gift of Dane Kennedy 2021 June 24 (Accession 2021.021)
  Kennedy, Dane Keith
  - NACBS Committee, 1999-2009; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - NACBS, 2004-2013; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - NACBS Nominating Committee, 2008; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - NACBS Reports, 2009-2010; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - NACBS Correspondence, 2009-2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - NACBS Committee Reports, 2009-2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - NACBS Capital Campaign, 2010; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - NACBS Committee Selection, 2010-2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - JBS - NACBS, 2010-2012; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - NACBS Hotel Contracts, 2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - NACBS Program Committee, 2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - NACBS Council Executive Committee Business, 2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - NACBS 2010 Meeting, MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - NACBS 2011 Annual meeting, MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - CUP / UCP Bids for JBS, 2011; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - NACBS 2012 Meeting, MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - CUP Contract / Transition, 2012-2013; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - JBS Editor Search, 2012-2013; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - NACBS membership, 2013; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - NACBS Meeting, 2013; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - NACBS 2014 Meeting, MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - NACBS 2015, MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Peter Stansky remarks at NACBS meeting, 2016 November 12; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - NACBS Guides, Undated; MS2187 Series 6 (Box 37, Folder 12)